Hurray, you're done implementing wire frames for the app! Now
comes the visual polish part, where we tweak the styles
and the views to make the app look awesome. Here
are the visual mocks, for what the app should look
like, when we're done. If you work with a designer,
they should also give you red lines. Red lines specify
everything from sizes, font styles, colors, spacing, et cetera. This
should help you achieve pixel perfect layouts that match the
visual mocks. How did we come up with these values?
Well we used the Android design guide, which has information on
metrics and grids, and we adapted them to fit our
app's needs. You can click on the link for more info.